♪I've been searching for the past♪
♪لقد كنت أبحث عن الماضي♪
♪This world and the face that looks like yours♪
♪هذا العالم والوجه الذي يشبه وجهك♪
♪When I start to write♪
♪عندما أبدأ الكتابة♪
♪I realize I'm slowly walking into danger♪
♪أدرك أنني أسير ببطء نحو الخطر♪
♪I thought it was destined loneliness♪
♪اعتقدت أنها كانت الوحدة المقدرة♪
♪Through lifetimes of pain, the memory stays clear♪
♪على مر العصور من الألم، تبقى الذكرى واضحة♪
♪You again and again, me step by step♪
♪أنت مرارا وتكرارا، وأنا خطوة بخطوة♪
♪Lost on the road searching for you♪
♪ضائع على الطريق أبحث عنك♪
=A Fleeting Dream=
=حلم عابر=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
Mr. Jiang, since you reached out to me,
السيد جيانغ، بما أنك تواصلت معي،
I guess you've come around
أعتقد أنك قد وصلت إلى هنا
and decided to work with me.
وقررت العمل معي.
I do have a task for you.
لدي مهمة لك.
Once it's done,
بمجرد الانتهاء من ذلك،
apart from sending you away,
بصرف النظر عن إرسالك بعيدًا،
there are some other benefits for you.
هناك بعض الفوائد الأخرى لك.
Considering how generous this offer is,
بالنظر إلى مدى سخاء هذا العرض،
I'm afraid
انا خائف
it's nothing simple.
إنه ليس شيئا بسيطا.
I want you
أريدك
to get rid of Pei Yuze.
للتخلص من باي يوزي.
You'll stop pretending, huh?
ستتوقف عن التظاهر، أليس كذلك؟
You surrendered first last night.
لقد استسلمت أولاً الليلة الماضية.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
I don't get it.
انا لم احصل عليها.
You don't get it?
أنت لا تفهم ذلك؟
If so...
إذا كان الأمر كذلك...
Let's jot your memory.
دعونا نسجل ذاكرتك.
Stop it!
اوقفها!
I'll jot your memory.
سأكتب ذاكرتك.
Second Master, you have a call from Mr. Wen.
سيدي الثاني، لديك مكالمة من السيد وين.
Did you hear that? Second Master, you have a call to answer.
هل سمعت ذلك؟ سيدي الثاني، لديك نداء يجب عليك الرد عليه.
"You have a call to answer."
"لديك مكالمة للرد عليها."
Actually, Yuze and I can manage it.
في الواقع، أنا ويوزي يمكننا إدارة الأمر.
You need not join us for the operation.
لا داعي للانضمام إلينا لإجراء العملية.
Wen Yuan isn't around, so I don't feel at ease.
وين يوان ليس موجودًا، لذا لا أشعر بالارتياح.
After sending you to the suburb and meeting Wen Xuan, I'll leave.
بعد أن أرسلك إلى الضاحية وألتقي بـ Wen Xuan، سأغادر.
Wen Xuan's investigation has led to a cousin of mine,
وقد أدى تحقيق وين شوان إلى ابن عمي،
who used to be a head candidate too.
الذي كان مرشحًا رئيسيًا أيضًا.
He studied medicine abroad.
درس الطب في الخارج.
He was at Pei Residence not long before my poisoning.
كان متواجدًا في منزل باي قبل فترة قصيرة من تسميمي.
I hope we can really find the lead to the antidote.
أتمنى أن نتمكن حقا من العثور على الترياق.
Granny!
جدتي!
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for having blocked your way.
لأنهم حجبوا طريقك.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
Jin Se, send the old lady home first.
جين سي، أرسل السيدة العجوز إلى المنزل أولاً.
We'll wait for you here.
سوف ننتظرك هنا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Let's get some rest while waiting for her here.
دعونا نحصل على بعض الراحة أثناء انتظارها هنا.
Yuze!
وجه!
Where's the medicine?
أين الدواء؟
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
It's alright. I'll be fine after some rest.
لا بأس. سأكون بخير بعد بعض الراحة.
Cold... I'm feeling so cold.
البرد... أشعر بالبرد الشديد.
Cold?
بارد؟
I'll get you a jacket.
سأحضر لك سترة.
Xinruo!
شينرو!
(Liu Xin Western Medicine)
(الطب الغربي ليو شين)
Yuze.
وجه.
Pei Yuze! Pei Yuze!
باي يوزي! باي يوزي!
Sir, have you seen this young man
سيدي هل رأيت هذا الشاب؟
sitting at the tea stall?
جالس في كشك الشاي؟
No.
لا.
Jiang Yao! Jiang Yao, this is bad!
جيانغ ياو! جيانغ ياو، هذا سيء!
- Xinruo, what's it with you? - This is bad. I went to buy Yuze a jacket.
- شينرو، ما بك؟ - هذا سيء. ذهبتُ لشراء سترة ليوزي.
- When I came down and turned around, - Calm down.
- عندما نزلت واستدرت، - اهدأ.
- Yuze was gone. I...
- يوزي ذهب. أنا...
Calm down. I'll have my men search for him in the city.
اهدأ. سأطلب من رجالي البحث عنه في المدينة.
Stay at home. I'll let you know at once if there's any news.
ابقَ في المنزل. سأُخبرك فورًا إذا كان هناك أي جديد.
No, that's not enough. The suburb...
لا، هذا لا يكفي. الضاحية...
That's right. I'll look for him in the suburb.
هذا صحيح. سأبحث عنه في الضاحية.
Xinruo. Xinruo!
زينرو. شينرو!
You heard that, butler.
لقد سمعت ذلك، يا كبير الخدم.
Go look for him!
اذهب وابحث عنه!
Sure...
بالتأكيد...
- Second Master!
- المعلم الثاني!
Have you seen this man?
هل رأيت هذا الرجل؟
No.
لا.
Miss, excuse me. May I know if you've seen this man?
يا آنسة، عذراً. هل لي أن أعرف إن كنتِ قد رأيتِ هذا الرجل؟
He's about this tall.
إنه طويل بهذا القدر.
- No. - I haven't seen him.
- لا. - لم أره.
Excuse me, miss.
عذرا سيدتي.
Have you seen this man?
هل رأيت هذا الرجل؟
No.
لا.
Please try to recall it.
من فضلك حاول أن تتذكره.
No, I truly haven't seen him.
لا، لم أره حقًا.
Sir, may I know if you've seen this man?
سيدي، هل يمكنني أن أعرف إذا كنت قد رأيت هذا الرجل؟
No.
لا.
Xinruo.
زينرو.
The night is falling.
الليل يهبط.
Head home now.
اتجه إلى المنزل الآن.
I'll keep looking for him.
سأستمر في البحث عنه.
You may head back if you want to.
يمكنك العودة إذا كنت تريد ذلك.
I'll look for him.
سأبحث عنه.
Xinruo. Xinruo!
زينرو. شينرو!
(Old Fengxiang Jewelry Store)
(متجر مجوهرات فنغ شيانغ القديم)
(Pei Residence)
(مسكن بي)
Miss Xinruo has had a cold.
السيدة شينرو أصيبت بنزلة برد.
Also, she's physically and mentally exhausted.
وهي أيضًا مرهقة جسديًا وعقليًا.
I'll get her a prescription. She'll be fine after a few days of rest.
سأحصل لها على وصفة طبية. ستكون بخير بعد بضعة أيام من الراحة.
Thank you, Dr. Fang.
شكرا لك دكتور فانغ.
Xinruo, be patient
شينرو، كن صبوراً
and rest well.
و استرح جيدا.
Just leave the rest to me.
فقط اترك الباقي لي.
Master Jiang!
سيد جيانج!
Master Jiang. Master Jiang, this is bad!
سيد جيانغ. سيد جيانغ، هذا سيء!
Miss Lian insists on going out
تصر الآنسة ليان على الخروج
and we can't stop her!
ولا يمكننا ايقافها!
Xinruo, you're still sick.
شينرو، أنت لا تزال مريضًا.
Go back to your room and get some rest.
عد إلى غرفتك واحصل على بعض الراحة.
Please leave me alone.
من فضلك أتركني وحدي.
Xinruo, where are you going at this late hour?
شينرو، إلى أين أنت ذاهب في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
I beg of you, please leave me alone.
أتوسل إليك، من فضلك اتركني وحدي.
I'll feel on edge
سأشعر بالتوتر
until Yuze is found.
حتى يتم العثور على يوزي.
Xinruo.
زينرو.
Pei Yuze might be...
قد يكون باي يوزي ...
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I thought I...
اعتقدت أنني...
Don't worry. See, I'm all fine.
لا تقلق، أنا بخير.
It was all my fault.
لقد كان كل هذا خطئي.
I was to blame for it.
لقد كنت مسؤولا عن ذلك.
When I turned around,
عندما استدرت،
I found out that you were gone.
لقد اكتشفت أنك رحلت.
And I couldn't find you anywhere.
ولم أتمكن من العثور عليك في أي مكان.
Don't blame yourself for that. Then I'll always stay by your side, okay?
لا تلوم نفسك على ذلك. سأبقى بجانبك دائمًا، حسنًا؟
Yuze, I...
يوزي، أنا...
Xinruo.
زينرو.
Xinruo!
شينرو!
Go away.
يبتعد.
Yuze...
وجه...
What exactly happened?
ماذا حدث بالضبط؟
After you left,
بعد رحيلك
I was kidnapped by the two tea stall servers.
لقد تم اختطافي من قبل خادمي كشك الشاي.
They tried to take me out of the city
لقد حاولوا إخراجي من المدينة
and get rid of me.
وتخلص مني.
I got out of the car when they let their guard down.
نزلت من السيارة عندما خففوا حذرهم.
Luckily, Wen Yuan found me.
لحسن الحظ، وجدني وين يوان.
I'm sorry. I...
انا اسف. انا...
What are you blaming yourself for?
لماذا تلوم نفسك؟
Get some rest first.
احصل على بعض الراحة أولاً.
Have a good sleep.
أتمنى لك نومًا جيدًا.
Jin Se has gone missing.
لقد اختفى جين سي.
Looks like that old lady we met this afternoon
يبدو أن تلك السيدة العجوز التي التقينا بها بعد ظهر هذا اليوم
was in cahoots with those tea stall servers.
كان متواطئًا مع هؤلاء العاملين في أكشاك الشاي.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
- But Second Master, you're still... - I'm alright.
- لكن يا سيدي الثاني، مازلت... - أنا بخير.
Father...
أب...
Jiao Jiao.
جياو جياو.
Father?
أب؟
I've finally seen you again.
لقد رأيتك أخيرا مرة أخرى.
You're already an 18-year-old lady. Still acting like a little girl, huh?
أنتِ فتاة في الثامنة عشرة من عمركِ. ما زلتِ تتصرفين كطفلة صغيرة، أليس كذلك؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Today's your birthday.
اليوم عيد ميلادك .
Quick, get yourself ready.
سريعًا، جهّز نفسك.
But aren't you...
ولكن أليس كذلك...
What's it?
ما هو؟
I think I had a nightmare.
أعتقد أنني كان لدي كابوس.
I dreamed about your passing.
حلمت برحيلك
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
Go ahead now.
إذهب للأمام الآن.
Yao is waiting for you.
ياو في انتظارك.
Go on.
إستمر.
What a lovely strawberry cake!
ما أجمل كعكة الفراولة!
Where's Mr. Jiang?
أين السيد جيانج؟
My father is busy.
والدي مشغول.
Let's not wait for him. Xinruo, blow out the candles now.
لا تنتظريه. شينرو، أطفئي الشموع الآن.
Sooner or later,
عاجلا أو آجلا،
you'll have to start calling Mr. Jiang Father.
سيتعين عليك البدء في مناداة السيد جيانغ بالأب.
You're unbelievable, Father!
أنت لا تصدق يا أبي!
Blow out the candles already.
أطفئ الشموع بالفعل.
You only get to unwrap your gift after making a wish.
لا يمكنك فتح هديتك إلا بعد تقديم أمنية.
You don't deserve Second Master! Get lost already!
أنت لا تستحقّ منصبًا ثانيًا! ارحل الآن!
What a shameless liar!
يا له من كذاب وقح!
No...
لا...
No!
لا!
- You're that murderer's daughter!
- أنت ابنة ذلك القاتل!
Xinruo.
زينرو.
Yuze.
وجه.
Great! You're finally here!
رائع! أنت هنا أخيرًا!
Without the antidote,
بدون الترياق،
I can't hold on much longer.
لا أستطيع الصمود لفترة أطول.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Yuze!
وجه!
Xinruo.
زينرو.
I can't get rid of the poison in me.
لا أستطيع التخلص من السم بداخلي.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
My days are numbered.
أيامي معدودة.
Xinruo.
زينرو.
Will you still be with me?
هل ستظل معي؟
I will.
أنا سوف.
No matter what your fate is,
مهما كان مصيرك،
I'll be with you.
سوف أكون معك.
Come with me, okay?
تعال معي، حسنًا؟
Don't leave me alone.
لا تتركني وحدي.
Come on.
تعال.
Here.
هنا.
Come.
يأتي.
Yuze.
وجه.
I'll stay by your side.
سأبقى بجانبك.
♪The city night silently envelops♪
♪ليلة المدينة تغلف بصمت♪
♪Hate and love♪
♪الكراهية والحب♪
♪His voice lingers by my ear♪
♪صوته يبقى في أذني♪
♪In this unavoidable dead end I encounter♪
♪في هذا الطريق المسدود الذي لا مفر منه الذي أواجهه♪
♪How can wounded love burn again♪
♪كيف يمكن للحب الجريح أن يحترق مرة أخرى♪
♪Leaving only his unpredictable smile♪
♪لم يبق منه سوى ابتسامته غير المتوقعة♪
♪My heart receives his gentle signals drop by drop♪
♪يستقبل قلبي إشاراته اللطيفة قطرة قطرة♪
♪Wounded wings try to rely on♪
♪الأجنحة الجريحة تحاول الاعتماد على♪
♪Secret love♪
♪الحب السري♪
♪Hidden in his most passionate embrace♪
♪مختبئ في أحضانه الأكثر شغفًا♪
♪Ignoring the noisy lights and wine♪
♪ تجاهل الأضواء الصاخبة والنبيذ ♪
♪Being a quiet cat in his arms♪
♪أكون قطة هادئة بين ذراعيه♪
♪Entwining the rest of my life, with no escape♪
♪تشابك بقية حياتي، بلا مفر♪